<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' ?>
<experience>
    <job>
        <company>Postquant Labs</company>
        <title>Senior Full-stack Engineer</title>
        <period>2026 — Now</period>
        <description>
            <bullet>Leading web3 integrations with EVM smart contracts and post-quantum cryptography.</bullet>
            <bullet>Adopted agentic development workflows end-to-end, cutting feature lead time by 70% (weeks to days).</bullet>
            <bullet>Built typed, composable RxJS pipelines over heterogeneous event streams, eliminating race conditions.</bullet>
            <bullet>Achieved 85% integration test coverage, enabling safe refactors and reducing regressions.</bullet>
            <bullet>Partnered with Product and Marketing on pixel-perfect, animated experiences.</bullet>
            <bullet>Shipping across 5 projects with full-stack React and TypeScript.</bullet>
        </description>
    </job>

    <job>
        <company>Kaizen Gaming</company>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer</title>
        <period>2024 — 2026</period>
        <description>
            <bullet>Senior engineer on the Live Betting team, serving 2M+ daily active users across 15+ markets.</bullet>
            <bullet>Built frontend systems with Vue 3, Vuex, Tailwind, and SignalR, processing realtime market updates.</bullet>
            <bullet>Architected a composable, functional rendering pipeline, cutting re-render time to milliseconds.</bullet>
            <bullet>Drove a 22% lift in player conversion and 35% reduction in time-to-bet through targeted UX work.</bullet>
            <bullet>Led cross-team architectural initiatives and mentored junior and mid-level engineers.</bullet>
        </description>
    </job>

    <job>
        <company>Aylo</company>
        <title>Backend Developer</title>
        <period>2023 — 2024</period>
        <description>
            <bullet>Modernized a 15-year-old Zend Framework 1 monolith, migrating to Laravel-based microservices.</bullet>
            <bullet>Enhanced content search with Elasticsearch, improving query latency and accuracy.</bullet>
            <bullet>Delivered PHP/Laravel/MySQL backend services serving hundreds of thousands of users.</bullet>
        </description>
    </job>

    <job>
        <company>Phenometry</company>
        <title>Full-stack Developer</title>
        <period>2022 — 2023</period>
        <description>
            <bullet>Full-stack engineer for Phi, a reactive, cross-platform 3D CAD web platform integrating with OnShape.</bullet>
            <bullet>Stack: Node.js, Express, TypeScript, Vue, PostgreSQL, three.js — from schema to WebGL rendering.</bullet>
            <bullet>Drove test coverage from 0% to 80%, introduced strict TypeScript, and built CI/CD pipelines.</bullet>
            <bullet>Reduced JS bundle size (20MB → 1.9MB), delivering sub-second Time to Interactive.</bullet>
            <bullet>Shipped a visual refresh, tablet/pen interaction layer, and Stripe billing integration.</bullet>
        </description>
    </job>

    <job>
        <company>Doppler SA</company>
        <title>Full-stack Developer / DevOps Engineer</title>
        <period>2020 — 2022</period>
        <description>
            <bullet>Full-stack development in PHP, Laravel, Lumen, Vue, SQL Server, and MariaDB.</bullet>
            <bullet>Architected CI/CD pipelines on GitLab and Docker, reducing deployment time by 80%.</bullet>
            <bullet>Delivered order-automation tooling and BI dashboards, saving an estimated 20 staff-hours per week.</bullet>
            <bullet>Built BI dashboards and ERP extensions adopted across departments.</bullet>
            <bullet>Mentored new employees in modern web development.</bullet>
        </description>
    </job>

    <foss>
        <company>Mattermost</company>
        <period>2022</period>
        <description>
            <bullet>Sponsored open-source contributor to the Electron desktop application, resolving Linux-specific bugs.</bullet>
        </description>
    </foss>

    <foss>
        <company>Organisation for Transformative Works</company>
        <period>2015 — 2021</period>
        <description>
            <bullet>Founded and coordinated the Greek translation team, growing it to 4 volunteers and delivering hundreds of thousands of translated words.</bullet>
            <bullet>Managed content workflows in WordPress and built internal tooling in jQuery.</bullet>
        </description>
    </foss>

    <plang>TypeScript</plang>
    <plang>JavaScript</plang>
    <plang>PHP</plang>
    <plang>Python</plang>
    <plang>SQL</plang>
    <plang>C</plang>
    <plang>bash</plang>
    <plang>HTML</plang>
    <plang>CSS</plang>
    <plang>SCSS</plang>

    <frontend>React</frontend>
    <frontend>Vue.js</frontend>
    <frontend>Nuxt.js</frontend>
    <frontend>Vuex</frontend>
    <frontend>Tailwind CSS</frontend>
    <frontend>RxJS</frontend>
    <frontend>Jest</frontend>
    <frontend>Vitest</frontend>
    <frontend>bun:test</frontend>
    <frontend>Zustand</frontend>

    <backend>Node.js</backend>
    <backend>Laravel</backend>
    <backend>PostgreSQL</backend>
    <backend>Netlify</backend>
    <backend>WebSockets</backend>
    <backend>Docker</backend>
    <backend>AWS</backend>
    <backend>Web3</backend>
    <backend>Git</backend>
    <backend>PHPUnit</backend>

    <lang>en</lang>
    <lang>gr</lang>
</experience>
