<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' ?>
<experience>
    <job>
        <company>Postquant Labs</company>
        <title>Full Stack Engineer</title>
        <period>2026 — Present</period>
        <description>
            Leading web integrations with EVM smart contracts and post-quantum cryptography.
            Applied agentic engineering principles end-to-end from ideation to verification, reducing feature lead time by 70% (from weeks to days).
            Modeled heterogeneous event streams with monadic principles and RxJS, eliminating an entire class of race conditions across async pipelines.
            Achieved 85% integration test coverage, enabling zero-headache refactors and reducing regression incidents.
            Partnered with Product and Marketing to deliver pixel-perfect, animated experiences.
        </description>
    </job>

    <job>
        <company>Kaizen Gaming</company>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer</title>
        <period>2024 — 2026</period>
        <description>
            Senior engineer on the Live Betting team, serving 2M+ daily active users across 15+ markets.
            Built and scaled frontend systems with Vue 3, Vuex, Tailwind, and SignalR, processing realtime market updates.
            Architected a composable, functional rendering pipeline that cut UI re-render time to milliseconds and reduced bundle size by 30%.
            Drove a 22% increase in player conversion rate and a 35% reduction in time-to-bet through targeted UX optimisations.
            Led cross-team architectural initiatives and mentored junior and mid-level engineers.
        </description>
    </job>

    <job>
        <company>Aylo</company>
        <title>Backend Developer</title>
        <period>2023 — 2024</period>
        <description>
            Modernised a 15-year-old Zend Framework 1 monolith, migrating to a Laravel-based microservices architecture.
            Enhanced content search with Elasticsearch, improving query latency and accuracy.
            Delivered backend services in PHP, Laravel, and MySQL serving hundreds of thousands of users.
            Collaborated with a React frontend team to expose new search APIs.
        </description>
    </job>

    <job>
        <company>Phenometry</company>
        <title>Full-stack Developer</title>
        <period>2022 — 2023</period>
        <description>
            Full-stack engineer for Phi, a reactive, cross-platform 3D CAD web platform integrating with OnShape.
            Stack: Node.js, Express, TypeScript, Vue, PostgreSQL, three.js — owning features from database schema to WebGL rendering.
            Drove test coverage from 0% to 80%, introduced strict TypeScript across 100% of the codebase, and built CI/CD pipelines automating release cycles.
            Reduced JS bundle size (20MB → 1.9MB), delivering sub-second Time to Interactive on average.
            Shipped a complete visual refresh, tablet/pen interaction layer, Stripe billing integration.
            Mentored new engineers.
        </description>
    </job>

    <job>
        <company>Doppler SA</company>
        <title>Full-stack Developer, DevOps</title>
        <period>2020 — 2022</period>
        <description>
            Full-stack development in PHP, Laravel, Lumen, Vue, SQL Server, and MariaDB across 5+ internal applications.
            Architected CI/CD pipelines on GitLab and Docker, reducing deployment time by 80% and eliminating manual release steps.
            Delivered order-automation tooling, saving an estimated 20 staff-hours per week.
            Built BI analytics dashboards and ERP extensions adopted across departments, improving operational reporting turnaround.
            Mentored 2 junior engineers and established team-wide code review and testing standards.
        </description>
    </job>

    <foss>
        <company>Mattermost</company>
        <period>2022</period>
        <description>
            Paid open-source contributor to the Electron desktop application (React, TypeScript), resolving Linux-specific bugs.
        </description>
    </foss>

    <foss>
        <company>Organisation for Transformative Works</company>
        <period>2015 — 2021</period>
        <description>
            Founded and coordinated the Greek translation team, growing it to 4 active volunteers and delivering hundreds of thousands of translated words.
            Managed content workflows in WordPress and built internal tooling in jQuery, improving operational efficiency.
        </description>
    </foss>

    <plang>Typescript</plang>
    <plang>Javascript</plang>
    <plang>PHP</plang>
    <plang>C</plang>
    <plang>Python</plang>
    <plang>Elisp</plang>
    <plang>Scheme</plang>
    <plang>(S)CSS</plang>
    <plang>bash</plang>
    <plang>SQL</plang>

    <tool>Vue</tool>
    <tool>React</tool>
    <tool>Tailwind</tool>
    <tool>Laravel</tool>
    <tool>Docker</tool>
    <tool>web3</tool>
    <tool>git</tool>
    <tool>node.js</tool>
    <tool>AWS</tool>
    <tool>Nuxt</tool>
    <tool>Vuex</tool>
    <tool>Websockets</tool>

    <lang>Greek</lang>
    <lang>English</lang>
</experience>
